um so we'll start so today we're here to
嗯，所以我们将开始，所以今天我们在这里
talk about cloud native Java and are you
谈论云原生Java，你呢？
and your company ready for cloud native
和您的公司准备好使用云原生
Java my name is Charlie Gracey I'm the
Java我叫Charlie Gracey我是
garbage collection architects on open j9
开放j9上的垃圾收集建筑师
Java VM
Java虚拟机
I forgot we had a picture you can reach
我忘了我们有一张你可以拍到的照片
me on Twitter
我在Twitter上
github anywhere if you wanted questions
github在任何地方，如果你想问问题
afterwards if we don't have time here
之后如果我们没有时间在这里
and I'm Jamie Lee Coleman I used to work
我是以前工作的杰米·李·科尔曼
on the docker team web sphere and I'm
在Docker团队网络领域，我是
now a developer advocate and again you
现在是开发者拥护者，而您又是
can reach me on Twitter so quick quiz
可以在Twitter上与我联系，因此快速测验
who here has been deploying Java cases
谁一直在部署Java案例
for years and is all ready to move to
多年以来，所有人都准备转移到
the cloud and if you are what are your
云，如果你是你的
approaches you decide it's so different
您认为这是如此不同的方法
you're just gonna throw everything away
你只是要把一切都扔掉
and rewrite it from scratch have you
并从头开始重写它
decided that clouds just sort of a small
决定云只是很小
thing bury your head wait for it to pass
东西埋了你的头，等待它过去
by and then keep going with your big
继续，然后继续与你的大
apps or you're gonna understand how
应用程序，否则您将了解
modern Java runtimes may actually help
现代Java运行时实际上可能会有所帮助
you in this new era of cloud to reuse
您将在这个新的云时代重用
and take advantage of the things you
并利用你的东西
already currently have anyone here doing
目前已经有人在这里做
any of those three things
这三件事中的任何一件事
so I've hands up I know ends up to be no
所以我举起手来，我知道最终不会
hands up to see you've gotta have one
举起手来看看你必须有一个
all right I'm hoping everyone had their
好吧，我希望每个人都有他们的
hand up for see that's what we're here
举起手来看看那就是我们在这里
for
对于
so what's really so special about the
那么关于
cloud and running things on top of your
云并在您之上运行事物
runtime so the cloud is and everyone
运行时，云便是所有人
talking but it makes all kinds of great
说话，但它使各种伟大
promises but it's very dynamic you don't
承诺，但它是非常动态的
have to have all of this Hardware
必须拥有所有这些硬件
yourself it'll scale quickly there's
你自己，它将迅速扩展
minimal costs upfront there's just a ton
前期成本最低，只有一吨
of things here that everyone's making
每个人在这里所做的事情
promises about but oh and the computer
承诺，但是哦，还有电脑
on demand just always what you've always
随需应变，一如既往
wanted
通缉
it's just cloud will save everything and
只是云将保存一切，
it's gonna make developing and working
这将使开发和工作
on your java applications or whatever
在您的Java应用程序上
working on easy and perfect that's great
轻松而完美地工作真是太好了
but the big thing that everyone sort of
但是每个人都有的一件大事
really leaves out especially if you're
真的省去了，特别是如果你
talking about Java and things like
谈论Java之类的东西
larger runtimes is that in the cloud all
更大的运行时是在云中
of your compute equals money it's a cost
您的计算等于金钱就是成本
for you and it's a constant sort of cost
对你来说，这是恒定的成本
all of the time it's not your hardware
一直不是你的硬件
anymore so you're paying somebody for
不再，所以您要为某人付费
the rights to this hardware and within
此硬件及其内部的权利
the cloud and this compute equals money
云计算，这等于金钱
really that translate down into dollars
真的转化成美元
per gigabyte of RAM used per hour that's
每小时使用的每GB RAM
kind of the main way that everyone is
每个人的主要方式是
charging for the cloud course there's
收费的云课程有
different things for numbers of CPUs and
CPU数量和
stuff but the biggest and most broad one
东西，但最大，最广泛的东西
that you see across all the different
在不同的地方看到的
cloud vendors is how many gigabytes of
云供应商有多少GB
RAM are you consuming per hour which
您每小时消耗的RAM数量
means in the Java world the size if your
表示在Java世界中，如果您
heap is really costing you money it's an
堆真的花了你很多钱
easy translation just changing the size
易于翻译，只需更改大小
of your - X MX you can literally see a
您的-X MX，从字面上您可以看到
difference in the cost you have per day
您每天的费用差异
per month per week that you're running
每周每月运行一次
in the cloud
在云端
so if you look at a normal workload here
因此，如果您在这里查看正常的工作量
it's great hand-drawn art everyone can
每个人都可以看到的很棒的手绘艺术
see my artistic skills so the demand of
看我的艺术能力，所以对
your application may go up and down over
您的应用程序可能会上下波动
time as you're going through with how
时间，因为你正在经历如何
many transactions how many customers are
很多交易有多少客户
hitting your website but and and how
点击您的网站，以及以及如何
does it really react to this different
它真的对这种不同做出反应吗
movement and different amount of
运动和不同量
resources hitting it so the way this is
资源击中它的方式是
normally handled is you have one big
通常处理的是你有一个大
server running all the time it's able to
服务器一直在运行
handle everything you over-provision it
处理您过度配置的所有内容
a little bit so that it can handle extra
一点点，以便它可以处理更多
transactions and an extra increase
交易和额外增加
Tuesday on Netflix when they're new
新人在Netflix上的星期二
shows come out they have extra demand so
节目出来，他们有额外的需求，所以
you over provision everything for the
您过度准备了一切
worst case basically everything above
最坏的情况基本上是上面的一切
the white line
白线
you're wasting that resource most of the
您浪费了大部分资源
time so if you have this VM running with
时间，如果您有运行此虚拟机
a two gig heap and most of the time
大部分时间都是两个演出
you're using less you're paying for two
您用得更少，您只需支付两个
gigs of heap image in the cloud so
堆映像在云中的演出，因此
that's actually a huge waste on you
这实际上是对您的巨大浪费
you could actually go and make some
你实际上可以去做一些
smaller comply times bring it up and
较小的遵从时间可以提高
down change your heap so then you're
向下改变你的堆，所以你
really only wasting at certain times can
真的只有在某些时候浪费
make it smaller again but they're still
再次缩小，但它们仍然
always a lot of waste so if you look at
总是很多浪费，所以如果你看
this one I can't figure out how to work
这个我不知道怎么工作
it anyway
无论如何
so over here so it's just throwing out
所以在这里，它只是扔出去
memory and throughput so when you're
内存和吞吐量，因此当您
ramping up an application you'll notice
增强您会注意到的应用程序
that it takes a while to get to maximum
要花一些时间才能达到最大
throughput and that you'll see you're
吞吐量，您会看到自己
here memory usage go up as the
这里的内存使用量随着
application is starting out and there is
应用程序开始了，有
always a sort of spike at the beginning
在开始时总是有点尖峰
particular when you're looking at a Java
特别是在您查看Java时
Runtime that's early on when the
运行时间早于
just-in-time compiler and things are
即时编译器
kicking in compiling lots of different
参与编译许多不同的内容
methods for you to have faster
让您更快的方法
throughput that's while your throughputs
吞吐量，而您的吞吐量
getting faster but they'll have these
越来越快，但他们会拥有这些
spikes and peaks of where they consume
消费高峰和高峰
large amounts of memory so in this model
大量的内存，因此在此模型中
you see that the cost here and extra
您会看到这里的费用和额外费用
times are two you get to your maximum
时间是两点
throughput and then also you have this
吞吐量，然后你也有这个
over peak usage of your memory at that
当时您的内存使用量超过峰值
point as well and any of time that
以及任何时间
you're not running and fast as you can
您没有尽可能快地运行
and using more memory you're paying
并使用更多的内存来支付
money that you shouldn't have to pay so
不用付钱的钱
this is more like what everybody would
这更像每个人都会
like almost instant on no extra memory
就像几乎没有存储空间一样瞬间
always using the amount of resources but
总是使用资源量，但是
we're gonna talk a bit about how maybe
我们将谈谈也许
we can get there so in your cloud
我们可以到达那里，因此在您的云中
demands one of them is that you want a
要求其中之一是您想要一个
small memory footprint as you scale out
扩展内存量小
more and more applications say in like a
越来越多的应用程式像
service or a micro services architecture
服务或微服务架构
you have multiple JVM s4 used to have
您曾经有多个JVM s4
one so any overhead that the JVM has
这样一来，JVM的所有开销
itself has now multiplied out and then
本身现在成倍增加，然后
as you spin out more instances of that
当您分解出更多实例时
you spin it out even further
你把它进一步旋转
everybody wants a small deployment size
每个人都想要一个小的部署规模
and you really want this scaling out so
而且您真的希望这种扩展
you want a very fast startup if you need
如果需要，您想快速启动
to handle more transactions or more
处理更多或更多交易
customers and it takes two minutes for
客户，这需要两分钟
your new instances to spin up you
您的新实例可以旋转您
probably just timed out or lost some
可能只是超时或丢失了一些
cost
成本
worse things took too long they left so
更糟糕的事情花了太长时间，他们离开了，所以
can we do all of these things and make
我们可以做所有这些事情并使
these improvements with a JVM is the
JVM的这些改进是
cloud so different for the JVM and a
云对JVM和
little quiz for everybody keep everyone
每个人的小测验让每个人
awake is the JVM no longer relevant eh
醒来是JVM不再相关了吧
yes it's irrelevant we should all move
是的，这无关紧要我们都应该搬家
to JIT no js' B maybe we might be able
不准J'B也许我们也许能够
to tune it and these types of things but
调整它和这些类型的东西，但是
it's gonna be difficult or no all the
这将是困难的，或者没有全部
JVM s are the same and that's what we
JVM是相同的，这就是我们
got so hoping again everyone's now
再次希望大家现在
picking a on this choice but we'll move
在这个选择上选择一个，但我们会继续前进
on so my answer to these things is open
因此我对这些事情的答案是公开的
j9 this is a new well new ish VM there
j9这是一个全新的全新虚拟机
was open source and donated to the
是开源的，并捐赠给了
Eclipse Foundation in September 2017
2017年9月的Eclipse Foundation
it's a completely open implementation of
这是一个完全开放的实现
the VM it uses EPL v2 and Apache 200
使用EPL v2和Apache 200的VM
license so it's free to basically use
许可，因此基本上可以免费使用
for whatever you want has a very non
因为无论你想要什么
restrictive licenses we're always
我们一直都是限制性许可
looking for new people come check things
寻找新朋友来检查的东西
out open pull requests open issues if
公开拉取请求公开问题，如果
you don't get an immediate answer I'd be
你不会立即得到我的答复
surprised King me personally I'll get
令我个人惊讶我会得到
you questions answered right away to get
您的问题马上得到回答
open j9 it's just a VM but if you want
打开j9，它只是一个VM，但是如果您想
the JDK as a whole I recommend going to
我建议将JDK作为一个整体
get all of your JD case from adopt open
从采用开放方式获取所有JD案例
JDK it's a program build environment run
JDK这是一个程序构建环境
by the London jug
由伦敦水罐
they build open JDK with hotspot with
他们用热点构建开放的JDK
open j9 all different releases are
打开j9的所有不同版本
building Knightley's building releases
奈特利大厦发布
it's a great place to go your binaries
这是去二进制文件的好地方
and you can then making some easy
然后您可以轻松一些
comparisons because they're built on the
比较，因为它们建立在
same sort of cadence and timeline as
节奏和时间表与
well so it's a very easy way to know
好吧，这是一个非常简单的方法
what you're getting in your JDK package
您在JDK软件包中得到的是什么
at any one time
在任何时候
sometimes when you're pulling it from
有时当您将其从
like apt-get or something on Linux
像apt-get或Linux上的东西
you're not quite sure which really
你不太确定哪一个
release what else has been done to it so
释放其他已完成的操作
these are some very vanilla ones you can
这些是一些非常香草的
go pick up as well of course every build
当然也要去捡
they do they also create a docker image
他们这样做，他们还创建了一个码头工人形象
for it as well
为此
new versions of dr. images based off of
Dr.的新版本基于的图像
this as their Java so you can go get
这是他们的Java，因此您可以获取
those as well from docker hub why is
那些来自docker hub的人为什么
open j9 so good for the cloud
打开j9对云非常有用
environment the world's greatest phone
环境世界上最伟大的手机
of all time was actually running Java ME
所有时间实际上都是在运行Java ME
and some of these small phones were
而其中一些小型电话是
running open j9 at the time so the roots
当时运行打开的j9
of open j9 come from a very small
j9的打开来自非常小的
embedded VM so with that the JVM Java ME
嵌入式VM，因此JVM Java ME
requirements at the time were very small
当时的需求很小
footprint lots of times you had very
足迹很多次
little ram you had large amounts of
你有很多的小公羊
large amounts of ROM sometimes but you
有时会有大量的ROM，但是您
had this very small amount of RAM you
拥有很少量的RAM
could use you have to have a very quick
可以使用你必须很快
startup people's games which was mostly
创业人的游戏，主要是
the use of Java on these phones again
在这些手机上再次使用Java
two minutes to start up your game you're
两分钟开始您的游戏
not playing the game very often it's too
经常不玩游戏
annoying and you also don't want your
烦人，你也不想
game to get only play well after you've
您玩完后只能玩得很好的游戏
played it for a while every time you
每次播放一阵子
start it up like you just don't want it
就像你不想那样开始
to be responsive two minutes after its
在其两分钟后做出响应
JIT at everything you really want that
准时完成您真正想要的一切
to happen early on so you have a
尽早发生，所以你有一个
consistent gameplay those who look very
外观一致的游戏
similar to the cloud requirements small
类似于云要求小
footprint you want as close to
您想要的足迹接近
instant-on as you can you want a really
您可以立即启动，
quick ramp up time just for the fact
为事实迅速增加时间
that all of these things as you go
这些东西随你去
through cost you money the more the more
通过花费您的钱越多
time you're not doing your peak the less
时间你没有达到巅峰
the more money you're paying for no
您为之付出的钱越多
reason so some sort of quick results
原因，所以某种快速的结果
here using open j9 have some links and
在这里使用开放j9有一些链接，
things I can share and I'll tweet later
我可以分享的东西，以后再发推文
you can go get some docker images and
你可以去拿一些码头工人的图像，
things and do a lot of these tests for
事情，并做很多这样的测试
yourselves and follow some of the simple
自己并遵循一些简单的方法
steps but startup time with open j9
步骤，但使用打开的j9启动时间
using our shared classes technology and
使用我们的共享课程技术和
this option QuickStart basically you can
此选项快速入门基本上可以
see that it's about 30% faster mileage
看到行驶速度快了30％
will vary here everyone should test on
每个人都应该在这里进行测试
their own don't always have to take my
他们自己不一定总要带走我
word for check things out yourself and
自己检查事物的单词，
the big one is footprint on a lot of
最大的是很多方面的足迹
things when you measure just
衡量时的事情
out-of-the-box switching from open hot
开箱即用的热切换功能
spot to open j9 60% is kind of one of
现货开j9 60％是其中一种
the average amounts of less footprint
减少足迹的平均数量
you see
你看
50 is the number I put on a lot but the
50是我投入的数字，但是
more we gather data more people are
我们收集更多的数据更多的人是
tweeting about things afterwards that's
然后在推特上发推文
really what it's closer to 60% so right
真的接近60％吧
away you could cut your cloud costs in
可以减少您的云成本
half for a lot of applications
一半用于很多应用
save your money your company money right
省钱省钱
away so if we remember this live from
如果我们还记得这个现场
before where I said this is sort of the
在我说这是之前
ideal where we want to get to with
我们想要去的地方的理想选择
memory footprint if you look at it so
如果您这样看的话，内存占用量
using one of these same tests with using
使用以下相同测试之一
open JDK 9 with hotspot this is the
用热点打开JDK 9，这是
memory consumption over time and here we
随着时间的推移内存消耗，在这里我们
go is open JDK with J 9 of the JDK 91 so
go是用JDK 91的J 9打开JDK的，所以
we actually get the own this one's
我们实际上得到了自己的
actually throughput sorry not memory so
实际上吞吐量不好意思不是内存所以
you actually get to peek through put
你实际上可以通过看一看
actually quite a bit quicker with open j
实际上，打开j会快很多
9 if we run with open j 9 using our t
9如果我们使用äôt在open j 9下运行
technologies which you get by using that
通过使用该技术而获得的技术
share classes option i showed earlier
我之前显示的共享类选项
just putting that on you'll get this
只要戴上它，你就会得到这个
pre-compiled JIT code in your cache
缓存中预编译的JIT代码
you'll actually see that you basically
你实际上会看到你基本上
have this instant on max throughput for
即时获得最大吞吐量
what you'll get for a max throughput
最大吞吐量将获得什么
using only a ot code since it's not
仅使用ot代码，因为它不是
doing all of the heavy JIT optimizations
做所有繁重的JIT优化
you could do you're going to be somewhat
你可以做，你会有点
limited here a max report and it makes
限制在这里最大报告，它使
even though it still does continue to do
即使它仍然继续做
some jibbing afterwards it makes some
之后会突然跳动
decisions early on based on the
早期基于
decisions it made before to do it
之前做的决定
quickly that kind of sort of limit you
很快这种限制你
as the releases keep happening this
随着发布不断发生
number but the green line and the blue
数字，但绿线和蓝
line keep getting closer with our last
与我们的最后一条线保持越来越近的距离
release it's quite a bit closer again
释放它又距离了
just those builds weren't ready before
只是那些构建还没准备好
we came here to put them in the chart
我们来这里是为了把它们放在图表中
they're just being built this week with
他们本周才被建造
a really just release and those will
一个真正的释放，那些会
continue hopefully to close the gap as
希望继续缩小差距
we go forward but it's just a decision
我们前进，但这只是一个决定
you can make again as another
你可以再做一个
alternative to actually get there even
实际到达那里的替代方法
quicker depending on where your max
更快，具体取决于您的最高位置
throughput is but if say you're on an
吞吐量是，但如果说您在
application that took only ran for two
仅用了两个的应用程序
or three minutes you are never getting
或三分钟你永远都不会
to the peak throughput in either hot spa
达到任一温泉浴场的峰值吞吐量
or open j9 before anyway you were
还是无论如何都要先打开j9
probably actually lower or around the
可能实际上更低或更低
same as what the AO t1 can get and you
与AO t1可以得到的一样
had that right from the beginning so
从一开始就有权利
that may be a trade off you're willing
这可能是您愿意付出的代价
to make depending on what your
取决于你的
applications doing so this sort of to
应用程序这样做是为了
cover things if you quickly here open j9
如果您快速在这里打开j9，请掩盖
has always been really designed to be
一直被真正设计为
small we've become the SE JVM as well so
小我们也已经成为SE JVM
it now works on small via small way of
现在，它可以通过小规模
memory and the scales all the way up to
内存和缩放比例一直到
really large powerful servers with
具有强大功能的大型服务器
terabytes of RAM and hundreds of CPUs it
兆兆字节的RAM和数百个CPU
can handle these constrained
可以处理这些约束
environments quite well and a lot more
环境很好，还有更多
things that have been coming online as
已经上网的东西
of late as well for like Auto detecting
对于自动检测也很晚
the urine docker images or other types
尿码头工人图像或其他类型
of virtualized environments and enabling
虚拟化环境并启用
things like idle detection and some of
诸如空闲检测之类的东西
these to turn off a lot of the extra
这些可以关闭很多额外的
things regifter the OS when you're not
当您不在时，事情会给操作系统留下深刻的印象
using it if you're at image has gone
如果你在图片上就用它
idle why do you still keep this memory
闲着你为什么还保留这个记忆
committed shrink down to their current
致力于缩小到目前
working set size hand that back the OS
支持操作系统的工作集大小指针
and you can grow again if you ever need
如果需要，您可以再次成长
the memory again so these types of
再次记忆，所以这些类型的
things are all coming online and being
一切都在线上
done in open j9 so for me I'm saying
在开放j9中完成，所以对我来说
that the open j9 jbm sort of saves the
打开的j9 jbm可以保存
day here it's something that we're
今天在这里，这是我们
really hoping that a lot of people will
真的希望很多人会
try and look at again it's got this
尝试再看一遍
really great license so anyone can
非常好的执照，所以任何人都可以
contribute and use it for whatever you
贡献并用于您的任何用途
need to use it for and it's there and
需要使用它，并且在那里
again don't take just my word actually
再次不要只听我的话
if you look and search on Twitter for
如果您在Twitter上查找并搜索
the app open j9 tag and just the end in
该应用程序打开j9标记，而结尾处
that user account there's tons of people
该用户帐户有很多人
talking about this regularly about just
定期谈论这个只是
like the bottom one here like just
就像这里最底层的一样
switched it and I draw from three
切换它，我从三个画
hundred Meg's to 130 Meg's of my memory
我的记忆从100兆到130兆
size and they kept their same or
大小，他们保持相同或
slightly better proof so I'll now move
稍微好一点的证据，所以我现在将移动
on to Jamie so Thank You charlie so
继续向杰米致谢查理如此
cloud mated Chava are we done
云交配的Chava我们完成了
yes there's nothing to see let's move
是的，没什么可看的，让我们前进
along not really I still need to react
一直以来，我仍然需要做出反应
attack my
攻击我的
ocation or no actually cloud native
位置或实际上没有云本机
introduces some new challenges so hands
引入了一些新的挑战，所以动手了
up for a good hands up Abbi what hands
举起好手举起阿比什么手
up for C so the correct answer is C yes
选择C，所以正确答案是C是
you do have to really architecture
你真的必须要建筑
application but it does create a lot of
应用程序，但确实创建了很多
new challenges so what you can run on
新挑战，让您可以继续前进
your JVM can outweigh the benefits that
您的JVM可能会超过
is true you could have the best JVM in
是的，您可能拥有最好的JVM
the world that could start up as quickly
可能很快启动的世界
like open j9 but if you run something
像打开j9一样，但是如果您运行某些命令
that's very heavy on top of it you're
最重要的是
going to not get any of the benefits in
不会得到任何好处
the cloud so let's have a look at
云，让我们来看看
Enterprise Java may 1998 started off as
Enterprise Java 1998年5月开始于
one projects then we had 10
一个项目，然后我们有10个
specifications 1420 and now we've got
规格1420，现在我们有了
lots of specifications in Java EE I'm
我在Java EE中有很多规范
going to quickly talk about open Liberty
要快速谈论开放自由
so this is something that you can run on
所以这是你可以运行的东西
your JVM it's a very very lightweight
您的JVM非常轻巧
application server and it's a new open
应用服务器，这是一个新的开放
source project I say news been around
我说消息源项目
about a year now from IBM design goals
距IBM设计目标大约一年的时间
of this application server were to be
该应用程序服务器的
efficient so it starts up quickly very
高效，所以它可以很快启动
low footprint it's only about 100 Megan
占地面积小，大约只有100兆
size I've managed to get about 10 of
我设法获得约10的尺寸
these running on a Raspberry Pi all in
这些都在树莓派上运行
docker container so that's a $20 piece
码头集装箱，所以这是一个20美元
of hardware so that's how small it is
的硬件，所以这是多么小
really simple to use we wanted to go
真的很简单，我们想去
from what we had with traditional
从我们传统的
WebSphere to create Liberty and then
WebSphere创建Liberty，然后
open Liberty and we want to make it very
开放自由，我们要做到非常
very simple to use so you can configure
使用非常简单，因此您可以进行配置
the whole server in one small XML file
整个服务器放在一个小的XML文件中
consistency I want to be able to deploy
我希望能够部署的一致性
this anywhere and I want to be
这在任何地方，我想成为
consistent every time so that was
每次都保持一致，因此
another thing we had to consider just
我们不得不考虑的另一件事
enough application server we don't want
我们不需要的足够的应用程序服务器
to have this big application server
拥有这个大型应用服务器
especially within the cloud when we
尤其是当我们在云中
scale up things we don't want to be
扩大我们不想成为的事情
scaling up these big application servers
扩展这些大型应用程序服务器
that are 5 10 gigabytes in size so again
大小为5 10 GB
we get the features we want from Java EE
我们从Java EE中获得了我们想要的功能
or micro profile and then it builds up
或微轮廓，然后建立起来
we have our application server just as
我们有我们的应用程序服务器
small as we need it good for virtualized
很小，因为我们需要它，因此对虚拟化非常有用
environments we have docker images for
我们有docker映像的环境
all these for this application server we
所有这些对于这个应用服务器，我们
have ones for micro profile and for
有一些用于微轮廓和
spring
弹簧
and of migration we don't want people to
在迁移方面，我们不希望人们
have to move to a new version and then
必须移动到新版本，然后
have to change their code we want it to
必须更改我们的代码
just work and agile ready very quick
刚好工作，敏捷就可以了
startup times you can literally get this
启动时间，你可以从字面上得到
application server running in about 10
应用服务器运行在大约10
seconds so this is simply how you can
秒，这就是您可以做到的
figure it feature manager to select the
选择功能管理器以选择
features you want the packaging type
您要包装的功能类型
here minify will squash the server down
这里minify将压缩服务器
as small as possible and runnable will
尽可能小且可运行
put it into a runnable jar for you so
把它放到一个可运行的罐子里给你
here's just an example of some maven
这只是一些行家的例子
dependencies so that's how you would
依赖关系，这就是你要的方式
configure your liberty with maven and
使用Maven配置您的自由，并
here's an example of form tale so very
这是一个形式故事的例子
similar so you've been deploying driver
类似，所以您一直在部署驱动程序
applications for years and you want to
多年的申请，您想
move to a cloud native approach you
迁移到云原生方法
decide cloud native is so different that
决定云原生与众不同
you need to throw everything away I know
你需要把一切都扔掉
we've already approached the slide do
我们已经接近幻灯片了
you decide do you decide that it's just
你决定你决定那只是
a storm
一场风暴
you're gonna hunker down and wait for
你会弯腰等待
clouds to pass or do you understand how
乌云密布还是你了解如何
mud Java runtimes let you reuse and
烂Java运行时让您重用和
extend your existing code so this is the
扩展您现有的代码，所以这是
big thing about micro profile is it
微型配置文件的大事是
allows you to build on the knowledge you
使您可以建立自己的知识
already have so everyone who's got
已经有，所以每个有
knowledge of Java EE can very easily use
Java EE的知识可以很容易地使用
that knowledge with micro profile so not
那些具有微观特征的知识
all cloud native challenges can be
所有云原生挑战都可能是
solved by the runtime so traditionally
传统上是由运行时解决的
and IBM has done this in the past quite
IBM过去已经做到了
a lot is where we've had very big
很多是我们拥有很大的地方
release cycles so once every six months
发布周期，因此每六个月一次
it gets the last two weeks of that
最后两周
release cycle and your infrastructure is
发布周期，您的基础架构是
hammered it's everyone's running builds
敲定这是每个人的运行版本
everyone's trying to get their code in
每个人都在尝试获取他们的代码
and basically your infrastructure all of
基本上所有的基础架构
a sudden growing store halts and you
突然增长的商店暂停了，您
have to pay for this very expensive
必须为此付出昂贵的代价
infrastructure because you have to
基础设施，因为您必须
handle that peak load so this is why the
处理该峰值负载，这就是为什么
cloud is great because when it comes to
云很棒，因为谈到
right at the end of your development
就在您开发的最后
cycle and those two weeks you've got
周期，那两个星期
this cloud which you can just pay for
你可以付钱的云
the extra resources for those two weeks
这两个星期的额外资源
so like you were saying before in your
就像你以前在你所说的那样
earlier slides you don't have to pay for
您无需付费的早期幻灯片
all this computing power all the time
所有这些计算能力始终
you can just pay for it when you need it
您可以在需要时付款
agile in microsomes is helps get code to
微粒体的敏捷性有助于获取代码
production a lot easier so you actually
生产容易得多，所以您实际上
don't need these release cycles anymore
不再需要这些发布周期
there's a product in IBM called message
IBM中有一种叫做message的产品
hub and they do this so so well they do
中心，他们做得很好
not have release cycles every day they
他们每天没有发布周期
produce their code it gets built and it
产生他们的代码，它被构建并
goes
去
straight to production and that is a
直接生产，这是一个
daily build thing and it works so well
日常构建的东西，效果很好
it means that we don't have to have this
这意味着我们不必拥有这个
time of the month where all of a sudden
一个月的时间突然
all our infrastructure is hammered so
我们所有的基础设施都受到重创
you have to think about when you develop
你必须考虑什么时候发展
micro services in a slightly different
微服务稍有不同
way and it also helps having all your
方式，还可以帮助您拥有所有
services separated because then you
服务分开，因为那你
don't have to do a massive bill to
不必为
redeploy your whole application you can
重新部署您的整个应用程序，您可以
just do a build which for this micro
只是做一个这个微
service again reducing costs on
服务再次降低了成本
infrastructure so Eclipse micro profile
基础设施，因此Eclipse微型配置文件
I presume you've all heard of Eclipse
我想大家都听说过Eclipse
micro profile this conference has been
本次会议的微简介
very micro profile centric Michael
以微轮廓为中心的迈克尔
profile came around I think it's around
个人资料出现了，我认为是
2016 basically the industry wasn't going
2016年行业基本不景气
Java EE wasn't going fast enough for us
Java EE对我们来说不够快
the clouds was already here by that
那个云已经在这里了
points and we kind of knew the way
点，我们有点知道方法
forward was using the cloud so a lot of
前锋正在使用云，所以很多
vendors came together there's actually a
供应商走到一起，实际上有一个
few more like Microsoft now and to
像现在和现在这样的微软
basically create their own specification
基本上创建自己的规范
for micro profile for Mike receivers so
对于麦克接收器的微型配置文件
it's a good chance you'll use rest api's
这是一个很好的机会，您将使用rest api的
when they were thinking about how all
当他们在想所有
these services going to communicate with
这些服务将与之通信
each other we needed a way to have these
彼此，我们需要一种方式来拥有这些
services decoupled otherwise it defeats
服务解耦，否则失败
the point of micro services I love
我爱的微服务的重点
WebSockets I think they're great but
WebSockets我认为它们很棒，但是
unfortunately that reduces very strong
不幸的是，减少了很强
coupling between your services and rest
服务与休息之间的耦合
api's and HTTP request seems like a
api和HTTP请求看起来像一个
really good way to provide a solution
提供解决方案的好方法
for that so Eclipse micro profile at the
为此，Eclipse微配置文件位于
beginning we had a look at the Java EE
开始我们看一下Java EE
spec and decided these are the
规格，并决定这些是
fundamental things for micro services
微服务的基础
rest client dependency injection JSONP
其余客户端依赖项注入JSONP
for parsing Jason Jason B for basically
基本上解析Jason Jason B
turning an object into Jason Ling about
把一个物体变成杰森·灵
back into an object again so you can
再回到一个物体，这样你就可以
share that object between your services
在您的服务之间共享该对象
and jax-rs but then all of a sudden
和jax-rs，但是突然之间
handling hundreds of collaborating micro
处理数百个合作的微观
services and they're evolving all the
服务，他们正在不断发展
time we can't just use those api's and
时间我们不能只使用那些api和
that's not enough so then came along
那还不够，所以随后出现了
micro profile added its own api's so
微型个人资料添加了自己的api，因此
configuration essentially you've got
基本上，您已经获得了配置
these hundreds of micro services I don't
我没有这数百种微服务
want to go into configure each one of
想进入配置每个
these micro services that is a pain in
这些微服务是痛苦的
the bum so basically configuration
烧伤，所以基本上配置
allows
允许
to externalize your configuration so in
外部化您的配置，以便
example for example a docker container
例如docker容器
you could mount in your config you can
你可以挂载在你的配置中
change it and it that could change
改变它，它可能会改变
configuration for say 10 or 100 micro
配置为10或100微
services also works dynamically which is
服务也可以动态工作
great you can actually change things
很棒，您实际上可以改变事情
while your application is running JWT so
当您的应用程序运行JWT时，
JSON web tokens they were already a
JSON Web令牌，它们已经是
standard and they work very well with
标准，并且它们与
HTTP requests so that seem like the
HTTP请求，因此看起来像
obvious choice of security fault
安全故障的明显选择
tolerance so fault tolerance we need a
容错，所以我们需要容错
way to make sure that if one of our
确保我们之一的方法
services is unreachable we have a
服务无法到达，我们有一个
fallback so my Netflix does this very
后退，所以我的Netflix非常做到这一点
well so the recommendation service the
好，所以推荐服务
bit at the top which recommends shows
推荐显示的顶部
you that is personalized to your viewing
根据您的观看个性化的您
habits now if that goes down do we
现在的习惯，如果那下降了，我们
really want a big black bar there or do
真的想要在那里有一个大黑酒吧
we really want Netflix not to work no we
我们真的希望Netflix不工作，不，我们
need a solution for that
需要一个解决方案
so fault tolerance essentially allows
因此容错性基本上可以
you to put a little annotation on top of
您在上方添加一些注释
your methods to give it another method
你的方法给它另一种方法
to fall back to so then we can have
回落到这样，那么我们可以有
another my preserver so for example
另一个我的保存人，例如
Netflix has a recommendation service a
Netflix有一个推荐服务
generic one that's always sitting there
总是坐在那里的通用
and if their main one goes down which is
如果他们的主要失败，那就是
customized to you then Michael profile
为您量身定制迈克尔个人资料
allows you to then fall back to this
然后让您回到这个
generic micro service this happens quite
通用微服务，这种情况相当普遍
a lot with Netflix but the users do not
在Netflix上很多，但用户却没有
know that is happening all they see is
知道正在发生的一切，他们所看到的是
the recommendation service is still
推荐服务仍在
working and it's recommending some shows
工作，并建议一些节目
to you you have no idea that is no
对你你不知道那是不
longer tailored to you so that is why
不再为您量身定制，这就是为什么
fault tolerance resumed juice and then
容错恢复果汁，然后
open ABI open API sorry is basically
打开ABI打开API抱歉基本上是
allows you to have a common set of API
允许您拥有一组通用的API
is for your vendors to use so you're
供您的供应商使用，因此您
deploying micro services that depend on
部署依赖于
other teams and you've noticed some
其他团队，你注意到了一些
errors in their service and it's caused
服务中的错误，是由于
your service to fail so what do you do
您的服务失败了，您该怎么办
do you blame the other team and tell
你责怪对方吗
them they need to sort out the racks you
他们他们需要整理架子
hold firm and just sit there and wait
坚定地坐在那里等
and trust that eventually they'll fix
并相信最终他们会解决
the problem or you take responsibility
问题或您承担责任
for gracefully coping with instabilities
优雅地应对不稳定
in the services so hands up for a let's
在服务中，所以举起手来
go that's fine hands up for be good
去那很好的举手就是好
thank you and hands up for C awesome so
谢谢你并举手致意C太棒了，所以
personally I would go with a and C I
我个人会选择和CI
would take responsibility for coping
将负责应对
with these situations but then I would
在这些情况下，但我会
also go back to the team
还回到团队
say you're lucky I code the way I did
说你很幸运，我用我以前的方式编码
because otherwise a service would have
因为否则服务将具有
gone down so personally I would've gone
我个人就倒下了
with agency so yes now we've got to
与代理商合作，是的，现在我们必须
handle hundreds of collaborating micro
处理数百个合作的微观
services and all of a sudden we have to
服务，突然之间我们不得不
consider things we never had to consider
考虑我们从来不需要考虑的事情
before all these services are
在所有这些服务之前
communicating with each other over a
通过一个彼此沟通
network and with monolith applications
网络和整体应用程序
we never had to worry about that before
我们之前不必担心
so hence the introduction of these three
因此，这三个的介绍
open tracing allows you to see exactly
开放式跟踪使您可以准确查看
all the requests that go in between your
您之间的所有请求
services and their responses from
服务及其回应
services so it allows tracking requests
服务，因此它可以跟踪请求
to be made a lot easier health check is
更容易进行健康检查
pretty much what it says micro service
几乎说微服务
are you alive yes good here's a request
你还活着是吗好这是一个请求
micro service are you alive no okay I'll
微服务，您还活着吗？
fall back to something else and metrics
退回其他内容和指标
basically allows you to get certain
基本上可以让你确定
metrics out of your micro services so
微服务中的指标
you can see the heap size you can see
你可以看到堆的大小
how much memory you're using how much
您正在使用多少内存
CPU usage you're using and you can even
您正在使用的CPU使用率，甚至可以
put custom metrics in there very easily
将自定义指标轻松放入
so you can put metrics in there but
因此您可以在其中放置指标
anything how many times is this method
这个方法多少次
being called how many times have I had
被叫了我几次
to fall back how many retries did it
退回多少次重试
take to hit a micro service so with
采取微服务，所以与
metrics you can pretty much customize it
您几乎可以自定义的指标
any way you want
你想要的任何方式
so you're the proud owner of a live
所以你是现场的骄傲的主人
production micro service but like me I
生产微服务，但像我一样
like my weekends and I don't like to sit
像我周末一样，我不喜欢坐
at a computer the whole weekend
整个周末都在电脑前
resolving issues so do you decide it's a
解决问题，您是否认为这是一个
no op due to encapsulation the great
没有操作，因为封装很棒
thing about micro services that's you
关于微服务的事情就是你
never need to know what's going on
永远不需要知道发生了什么
inside you write everything to STD apps
您将所有内容都写入STD应用
X Factor the 12 factor net tells you
X Factor 12因子网告诉您
that's all you need to do or do you
这就是您需要做的或要做的
instrument your services with health and
通过健康的方式来衡量您的服务
ku probes metrics with Prometheus and
ku使用Prometheus和
use open tracing with Zipkin so has it
与Zipkin一起使用开放式跟踪
for a good ants B as of C cool yeah so
换成C的好蚂蚁B很酷，所以
definitely see basically if you put all
肯定基本上看，如果你把所有
that into your mic receivers you can
可以放入麦克风接收器中
figure out what's going on very very
弄清楚发生了什么
quickly or as if you didn't it's gonna
很快，或者好像你没有
take you a long time to debug these
需要很长时间调试这些
things so everyone probably thinks well
事情，所以每个人都可能认为很好
why can't I do all this with a service
为什么我不能通过一项服务来完成所有这些工作
mesh what why not I mean kubernetes does
网格为什么我不是说kubernetes呢
a lot of these things yes kubernetes
这些事情很多，是kubernetes
does
确实
does the retry and the timeout and
重试和超时并
circuit breaker in the bulkhead but
隔板中的断路器，但
kubernetes does not offer anything in
kubernetes不提供任何服务
terms of fallback if I can't hit my
如果我无法击中我的后备条款
micro service I need it to fall back to
微服务，我需要它回落
something like Netflix does and that's
像Netflix这样的东西
where this comes into play now you can
现在它可以发挥作用了
mix and match so you can use kubernetes
混合搭配，您可以使用kubernetes
for the top four or you could use
前四名，或者您可以使用
kubernetes for one of the top four and
kubernetes是前四名之一，
have your application do did the rest
让您的应用程序完成其余的工作
it's entirely up to you but
这完全取决于你，但是
unfortunately your service mesh does not
不幸的是，您的服务网格无法
solve the problem so packaging for
解决问题，所以包装
deployments I'm pretty sure well as far
到目前为止，我很确定
as I'm aware I haven't come across a
据我所知，我还没有遇到过
cloud that doesn't support
不支持的云
Dakka Dakka basically in my opinion
达喀达喀基本上在我看来
docker has pushed micro services to
码头工人已将微服务推向
where they are now docker came around I
他们现在在哪里码头工人来到了我身边
think just before just before Michael
在迈克尔之前思考
profile it made us look at the world in
简介让我们着眼于世界
a different way so before we had these
所以在我们拥有这些之前
big monolithic applications and when you
大型整体应用以及何时
start sticking them a document Aynor
开始给他们贴文件Aynor
all of a sudden it doesn't make as much
突然间它赚不了多少
sense as it once did you've got all
感觉就像曾经一样
these docker containers all
这些docker容器全部
communicating on the same network so why
在同一网络上通信为什么
don't you split your application out so
你不把你的申请分开吗
I'm gonna talk a little bit about layers
我要谈几层
so this is bad
所以这不好
this is good I'll explain why now
这很好，我现在解释为什么
because docker is very very good at
因为码头工人非常擅长
sharing layers if they are the same so
共享图层（如果相同）
for example here it would share the OS
例如在这里它将共享操作系统
layer it would share the JVM layer but
它将共享JVM层，但是
this layer won't be shared because now
该层将不会共享，因为现在
you've got this big fat jar whereas if
你有这个大胖子罐子，而如果
you had two of these you could then
你有两个你可以
share the application layer which would
共享应用层
bring down the size of your dock
减小码头的尺寸
repository and it also makes startup
仓库，它也可以启动
time of your document owners a lot
您的文档所有者的时间很多
faster so your boss asking you to
更快，所以你的老板要求你
recommend an open technology stack for
推荐一个开放的技术栈
deploying micro services do you
您部署微服务吗
recommend eclipse open j9 to optimize
推荐eclipse open j9进行优化
your runtime characteristics and cost
您的运行时特征和成本
for the cloud do you recommend micro
对于云，您推荐微型吗
profile to add resilience monitor
配置文件以添加弹性监视器
ability and more in a vendor-neutral way
与供应商无关的能力
or do you recommend the right size will
还是您建议合适的尺寸
runtime with a broad open spec support
具有广泛开放规范支持的运行时
open liberty yep or or live up so I'm
是的，是自由的开放还是活下去，所以我
going to start with D hands up for D and
从D开始举起手来为D和
C be a-ok
没关系
so yeah correct one of the things is
是的，正确的一件事是
here I want you to take away from this
在这里我要你从中带走
is vendor-neutral
与供应商无关
so spring is very easy to learn and you
所以春天很容易学，你
can get learning you can get up and
可以学习，可以起来
running with spring very quickly you are
很快地和春天一起跑步
locked into one vendor and that vendor
锁定在一个供应商中，该供应商
has control of everything which is a
拥有一切的控制权
really really big problem if they decide
如果他们决定，那真的是一个很大的问题
to make a decision you don't like tough
做一个你不喜欢艰难的决定
you've got to deal with it whereas micro
你必须处理它，而微观
profile has so many vendors in putting
个人资料中有很多供应商
him from inputting specs into it and
他从输入规范到
inputting their their ideas that it's
输入他们的想法是
very very difficult for basically
基本上很难
something to happen without without your
没有你的事情会发生
input essentially creating issues for
输入本质上为
you also you're not locked into one
你也不会被限制在一个
vendor for support you're locked in you
供应商为您提供支持
can now go to multiple vendors to get
现在可以去多个供应商那里
support hopefully which will bring down
希望支持会降低
your cost a little bit so I'm going to
你花了一点钱，所以我要
show you a little bit of fallback code
向您展示一些后备代码
just to show you how simple it is to do
只是向您展示这是多么简单
this we have a website open Liberty dot
这个我们有一个网站开放的自由点
IO and there is loads and loads of
IO和负载
guides on here there's some open Liberty
这里有一些开放的自由指南
specific ones but then we have loads to
具体的，但是我们有负担
do with micro profile and fault
处理微观轮廓和故障
tolerance is stuff to do with JWT
容忍与JWT有关
some of them are interactive which is
其中一些是互动的，这是
quite nice but for example this is fault
很好，但是例如这是错误
tolerance this is all you need all you
宽容这就是你所需要的
need to do is that one import and the
需要做的是一次进口和
annotation and basically all that does
注释和基本上所有的工作
is basically say if this fails fallback
基本上说这是否失败
to another method here's the fallback
另一种方法是这里的后备
method
方法
so essentially what Netflix are doing
所以本质上Netflix在做什么
this situation this fallback method
这种情况下的后备方法
would go call another service and that's
会去打电话给另一个服务，那是
how simple it is to do fallback in micro
在微型计算机上进行回退有多简单
profile also I'm going to show you a
个人资料，我也要给你看
little bit of configure how to do config
一点点配置如何做配置
here's my config file it's in just a
这是我的配置文件
product properties file and I've got
产品属性文件，我已经
stuff in there like the port number is
那里的东西，如端口号是
it maintenance so you can change boolean
它维护，因此您可以更改布尔值
to true or false depending if you want
判断是真还是假
to like stop request going to a certain
喜欢停止请求去某个
micro service if you're doing
如果您正在做微服务
maintenance that could also come up with
维护也可以
a message saying all this websites in
一条消息说所有这些网站位于
maintenance try again later or something
维护稍后再试
like that and then to import that all
这样，然后导入所有
you have to do is this import here and
您要做的就是在这里导入
then simply inject the config like so
然后像这样简单地注入配置
and now that
而现在
Figg will be this integer here will
Figg将是这个整数
there be the port number from your
从您的端口​​号
configuration and you can do also do
配置，您也可以做
this dynamically so what your
这是动态的，所以你
application is running you can change
应用程序正在运行，您可以更改
the configuration and your application
配置和您的应用程序
will pick it up instantaneously I from
会立即从我那里拿起
me I think that is its doo-doo-doo-doo I
我，我想那是它的doo-doo-doo-doo
here's some useful links so we've got a
这是一些有用的链接，所以我们有一个
link to so there's a link to the open j9
链接到，所以有一个指向打开的j9的链接
site there's a link to the adopt open
网站上有一个采用开放的链接
JDK sites where you can get all the new
您可以在其中获得所有新功能的JDK网站
versions Mike profile to i/o the clips
版本Mike个人资料到I / O剪辑
micro file sites the website I just
微型文件网站我刚刚建立的网站
showed you with all the guides on and
向您展示了所有指南，以及
the open ability website and that is the
开放能力网站，那就是
end of our presentation thank you yeah
我们的演讲结束谢谢
do we have any questions sorry right now
我们现在有任何疑问对不起吗
available there is open j9 for Java 8 9
可用的是针对Java 8 9的开放式j9
and 10 are in maintenance because
和10个正在维护中，因为
they're no longer releases 11 and I
他们不再发布11，而我
think 11 is selasa are adopt there's
认为11是selasa被采用
nothing older than Java 8 and what open
没有比Java 8更古老的版本了
j9 source code it's open source works
j9源代码，它是开源的作品
the same source code works from 8 and
相同的源代码适用于8和
every release newer we build all the
每次发布更新，我们都会构建所有
same virus from it but it doesn't
相同的病毒，但不是
support anything older than 8 basically
基本上支持8岁以上的任何事物
for comparing open j9 to the open JDK
比较开放j9和开放JDK
releases the goal is to be same day but
发布目标是当天，但
it's more likely to be same week right
更有可能是同一周
here
这里
a lot more of those have been all
这些都更多了
resolved now as the it's open I don't
现在解决了，因为它是开放的，我没有
want to say all of them have been it but
想说所有的都是
if you did encounter another one that's
如果您确实遇到了另一个
still there something like that it
还是那样的东西
should have been resolved cause like the
应该已经解决了原因
last one I could think of was Jabba
我能想到的最后一个是贾巴
Liang management api's we've now
梁管理api的我们现在
implemented those all in the right
正确执行那些
namespace and things have moved a lot of
命名空间，事情已经发生了很多变化
that actually got resolved for you by if
的确为您解决了
you're a Java nan you're new or with
您是Java的新手还是新手
modules because a lot of things had to
模块，因为很多事情不得不
be listed as JDK internal so they ended
被列为内部JDK，所以他们结束了
up in exactly the same namespace at that
在那个完全相同的名称空间中
point for those ones any of questions
为那些问题指出任何问题
yes so there's really two big solutions
是的，所以实际上有两个大解决方案
for that so one that it's not my normal
为此，这不是我的正常
recommended solution is you can actually
推荐的解决方案是您实际上可以
mount volumes when you start up your
启动时挂载卷
doctorate mates so you hit map a volume
博士学位，所以你打地图
and have that to be where your shared
并将其作为您共享的地方
memory is the other alternative which is
内存是另一种选择
usually what I recommend to people if
通常我向人们推荐的是
you're building your own document
您正在构建自己的文档
because you're having something
因为你有东西
installed with your application as well
与您的应用程序一起安装
as part of building your docker image
作为构建docker映像的一部分
when you're building your application
在构建应用程序时
layer if you're doing it in layers that
层，如果您正在将其分层
way then as soon as you're done with the
然后，一旦您完成
install I would have it actually run the
安装我会让它实际运行
application once so that it actually
申请一次，以便它实际上
creates the share classes cache for you
为您创建共享类缓存
and then it becomes part of your doctor
然后它成为您的医生的一部分
application layer
应用层
yeah you'd have to do it once otherwise
是的，否则你必须做一次
you be otherwise you would lose it every
否则你会失去一切
time like you said and one more here
像你说的那样，还有一个
faster startup I use it every day sorry
更快的启动我每天都用它对不起
I used it every day until a few months
我每天都用到几个月
ago when I got a MacBook now we now have
以前当我有了MacBook时现在我们有了
goods cuz open j9 wasn't available on
商品Cuz Open J9在
Mac until this last release so I just
Mac，直到最后一个版本，所以我只是
haven't switched everything with travel
并没有改变旅行的一切
don't touch your laptop the week before
一周前请勿触摸笔记本电脑
you present but I've always on my
你在场，但我一直在我
Windows laptop I always used open j9 or
我一直使用Windows笔记本电脑打开j9或
the IBM JVM at the time with a shared
当时使用共享的IBM JVM
classes cast so startup was always quite
上课，所以启动总是很
a bit faster and similarly the heap
快一点，堆也一样
savings for a rich desktop client like
为丰富的桌面客户端节省的资金，例如
that aren't quite to the same because
不太一样，因为
well one if you don't go change your ear
好吧，如果你不去改变你的耳朵
I and I file anyway to change some of
我和我仍然提出更改一些
the settings you're just going to use
您将要使用的设置
more because it gives it more so it's we
更多，因为它提供了更多，所以是我们
can't go less than that but even when I
不能比那少，但即使当我
didn't lower it down I would say it's
没有降低它，我会说是
more on the order of about 20 percent 15
大约更多20％15
percent of less memory but I usually am
内存减少的百分比，但我通常是
really pushing it hard anyway so it
无论如何真的很难推动它
usually ends up using more but when I
通常最终会使用更多，但是当我
was doing plug-in development for a
当时正在为
while I definitely saw some pretty nice
虽然我肯定看到了一些不错的东西
improvements to go be able to start up
可以启动的改进
my my plugin all the time as I was doing
我一直在做我的插件
that development spinning up new images
这项发展为新形象锦上添花
all the time
每时每刻
like as terms is the GC for moving
就像移动GC一样
things for us to give it back depending
我们要退还的东西取决于
on the GC policy we there's different
在GC政策上，我们有不同之处
ways some of them are like the more
他们中有些人喜欢的方式
region based collectors like we have
像我们这样的地区性收藏家
balance which is comparable to G one and
等于G one的余额，并且
those types of collectors it is quite a
那些类型的收藏家是相当
bit easier but to do some of these we do
容易一些，但要做一些我们要做的
actually end up having to compact the
实际上最终不得不压缩
heap so that we can give away the high
堆，以便我们可以放弃高
end of the address most of the time so
地址的大部分时间是这样
we would do that at different times so
我们会在不同的时间这样做
one of the major times we do it is when
我们这样做的主要时间之一是何时
we detect it your application is going
我们检测到您的应用程序正在运行
idle so at that point you're not
闲着，所以那时候你不是
consuming many CPUs so we are hopefully
消耗很多CPU，所以我们希望
not if it's idle for right so then we'll
如果闲着没事，那么我们会
actually we will do a compact and
实际上，我们会做一个紧凑的
contract the heap and M advise it back
收缩堆，M建议它回来
to the OS sometimes we end up how to do
有时我们最终会怎么做
that at runtime as well but usually we
在运行时也是如此，但是通常我们
try to avoid that as outside of the idle
尽量避免那样的闲置
phase the way we keep it smaller usually
通常将其保持较小的阶段
is we just actually don't expand we
是我们实际上不扩大我们
don't take all the memory that you've
不要占用你所有的记忆
given us and less we're spending too
给了我们更少的钱
much time in the garbage collector cool
很多时间在垃圾收集器中很酷
thank you everybody
谢谢大家
Thanks
谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]